<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Uç! Uç! | concert</title>
        <link>https://ucuc.info/concert</link>
        <description>concert category on Uç! Uç!</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <image>
            <title>Uç! Uç!</title>
            <url>https://ucuc.info/assets/common/writ-icon-512.png</url>
            <link>https://ucuc.info</link>
        </image>
        <category>album</category>
        <category>concert</category>
        <category>performance</category>
        <category>single</category>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue Aug 20 2024 20:37:34 GMT+0100 (British Summer Time)</lastBuildDate>
        <copyright>All rights reserved 2024, Uç! Uç!</copyright>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <generator>writ-cms</generator>
        <atom:link href="https://ucuc.info/concert/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Karga Fest]]></title>
            <link>https://ucuc.info/concert/karga-fest</link>
            <guid>https://ucuc.info/concert/karga-fest</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
      <div><img src="https://ucuc.info/concert/karga-fest/karga.jpg" alt="undefined"></div>
      <p>Early New Year Festival at Karga Kadıköy - December 28th  </p>
<p>We’re thrilled to invite you to our Early New Year Festival on December 28th at Karga Kadıköy! We’re a group of friends who’ve put together something really special, and we’d love for you to be a part of it.   </p>
<p>Uç Uç will kick things off with some amazing tunes.  </p>
<p>Upstairs is Boiling, and the energy is going to be.. hmm, expect the unexpected. </p>
<p>Şu Güzel İnsanlar will bring some chill vibes with their soothing melodies.  </p>
<p>Erdem, Özün, and Ozan will close the night with an epic drum trio performance.  </p>
<p>And just when you think the night is winding down, we’ll keep the energy high with a DJ set that’ll keep you dancing until the very end!  </p>
<p>Downstairs, our friends will be showcasing and selling their handmade creations, so it’s a great chance to support local artists and find something unique.  </p>
<p>We’ve put our hearts into organizing this festival, and we’re making sure it’s going to be an amazing night full of great music, creativity, and positive vibes.   </p>
<p>So mark your calendars for December 28th, and come celebrate with us at Karga Kadıköy! We can’t wait to see you there!  </p>

    ]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
