<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Uç! Uç! | album</title>
        <link>https://ucuc.info/album</link>
        <description>album category on Uç! Uç!</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <image>
            <title>Uç! Uç!</title>
            <url>https://ucuc.info/assets/common/writ-icon-512.png</url>
            <link>https://ucuc.info</link>
        </image>
        <category>album</category>
        <category>concert</category>
        <category>performance</category>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue Mar 04 2025 17:24:48 GMT+0000 (Greenwich Mean Time)</lastBuildDate>
        <copyright>All rights reserved 2024, Uç! Uç!</copyright>
        <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
        <generator>writ-cms</generator>
        <atom:link href="https://ucuc.info/album/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feeding the crows by hand]]></title>
            <link>https://ucuc.info/album/feeding-the-crows-by-hand</link>
            <guid>https://ucuc.info/album/feeding-the-crows-by-hand</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
      <div><img src="https://ucuc.info/album/feeding-the-crows-by-hand/kapak.png" alt="Our live performance album, recorded at Yuva, one of the most special venues in Kadıköy, at Karga, has been released."></div>
      <p>Our live performance album, recorded at Yuva, one of the most special venues in Kadıköy, at Karga, has been released.</p>
<p>You can listen to the album on all streaming platforms and Bandcamp.</p>
<p>As always, it&#39;s hard to define the genre of the album. It&#39;s the result of a mutual conversation and understanding. The music was composed and recorded on the spot as an improvisation. So, everything you see and hear in this performance is created and performed &#39;right then and there.&#39; It cannot be repeated and could not have been predicted beforehand. We think that music thrives when no one knows anything about it beforehand.</p>
<p>The album was mixed and mastered by Ercan Bektaş Ülger, and the cover design was done by Onur Nevşehir :)</p>
<p>There is also a video of our performance, recorded by the @idgk.tv team, which you can watch on YouTube.</p>
<p>So much love, Uç! Uç!</p>

    ]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Faerie Journey]]></title>
            <link>https://ucuc.info/album/faerie-journey</link>
            <guid>https://ucuc.info/album/faerie-journey</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
      <div><img src="https://ucuc.info/album/faerie-journey/kapak.jpg" alt="The spirit of that music corresponds to the experiences of a fairy who suddenly wakes up in another universe and to the transformational magnificence of her inner world, that feast, that complexity, that tranquility and that emptiness."></div>
      <p>O dear listener !</p>
<p>The album you&#39;re listening to is just a spiritual experiment that the musicians do on themselves.</p>
<p>The spirit of that music corresponds to the experiences of a fairy who suddenly wakes up in another universe and to the transformational magnificence of her inner world, that feast, that complexity, that tranquility and that emptiness.</p>
<p>Listen at your own risk.</p>
<p>We hope that these sounds, which musicians entered into the studio without any expectations, played for 4 hours and come out without any pre-talk and determination, will take you on this journey too.</p>
<p>In this process, where the musicians and the fairy are trying to find themselves, the aim is only to search for ourselves.</p>
<p>Everything was composed at that moment and recorded live.</p>

    ]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Constant Fear of Being Judged (By You)]]></title>
            <link>https://ucuc.info/album/the-constant-fear-of-being-judged-by-you</link>
            <guid>https://ucuc.info/album/the-constant-fear-of-being-judged-by-you</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
      <div><img src="https://ucuc.info/album/the-constant-fear-of-being-judged-by-you/kapak.jpg" alt="The spirit of that music corresponds to the experiences of a fairy who suddenly wakes up in another universe and to the transformational magnificence of her inner world, that feast, that complexity, that tranquility and that emptiness."></div>
      <p>With their debut album “The Constant Fear of Being Judged (by you)” they bring forward the calm and rough, raw and refined sounds. Acoustically and polyrhymically played drums combined with texture based piano playing, an underground sound engineer with a guitar playing traditional and unconceptual melodies with a bass whose unstability sustain stability. A meditation like jazz music, which is almost in the realms of neo-classical music, meets sound design and experiments of emotions and sounds. It is like a calm carnaval where everybody gets a smile on their faces when everybody joins the spiritual wave that the band creates. Uç! Uç! makes an honest and conceptual minimal music which turns into something bigger with everystep into the music.</p>
<p>Drums: Mustafa Kemal Emirel<br>Piano: Onur Nevşehir<br>Electronics: Barış Ergün<br>Electric Guitar: Bahadır Kartal<br>Bass Guitar: Taylan Öner<br>Recording: Sinan Sakızlı @İstanbulHayyamStudios<br>Editing: Alican Vatanperver<br>Mixing: Barkın Engin<br>Mastering: Güven Ersoysal @İstanbulBabajimStudios  </p>

    ]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
